Saurav K. Thakur

Futurist

Birgunj, Nepal 44500 saukrthak@gmail.com 9779804296330

Savvy 17 y.o. entrepreneur with an insatiable thirst for knowledge and a knack for problem-solving. Karate Black Belt. Public Speaker.

Led successful SaaS startups and worked with top companies worldwide. Hands-on experience in business, marketing and operations.

Creative side: photography, singing, playing guitar, traveling and exploring life.

Work Experience

Head Of Content

Orbis Labs

February 2022 to December 2022

• Oversaw a team of writers/editors producing ~50 content pieces a month, ranging from blogs to SM posts, to ensure a cohesive marketing approach.

Social Media Manager

Ardana

July 2021 to December 2022

• Coordinated the company's advertising and activity on numerous social networks, including Twitter, Telegram, Reddit, and Discord.

Sr. Growth Lead

Hype Partners - Remote August 2021 to August 2022

• Worked with a 150+ team to create and implement strategies that helped our clients grow their businesses.

Community Lead & Mental Health Advocate

Hope Foundation DAO - Remote April 2021 to December 2021

• Set out to build a web 3.0 community that could impact the global mental health crises through proactive mental health awareness & initiatives.

Community Manager

Guarda Wallet - Remote April 2020 to August 2021

• Interacted with customers, employees, and vendors on a daily basis; aimed to increase product awareness, attract new customers, and retain existing customers.

• Social media management, content creation (blog posts and articles), user research and feedback from customers, answering their questions and concerns, customer support (on Twitter, Reddit, and Telegram), and events planning (meetups, conferences).

Professional Freelancer

Upwork - Nārāyanī, Nepal March 2017 to June 2021

Worked w/ 100+ clients to build a creative marketing strategy that boosted their community growth by big numbers.

Social Media Manager & Ambassador

Swapzone - Remote April 2020 to April 2021

- Set up social media accounts for Swapzone and its products.
- Created strategy and content calendars for each account to help get the right message out to our customers at the right time, as well as reflect the brand voice.

Advisor & Marketing Lead

Project TradeX - Nepal November 2020 to January 2021

• Conceptualized and executed on multi-channel campaigns across the prospect and customer lifecycle, ensuring the alignment of communications and messaging across all channels.

Brand Ambassador

ChangeNOW.io - Remote April 2020 to October 2020

• Responsible for growing the company's social media presence, managing its customer service team, and making sure that ChangeNOW is always on top of what's happening in the space.

Education

School Leaving Certificate (High School) in Science

Alpine Secondary School

Skills

- Leadership (5 years)
- Digital Marketing (4 years)
- Entrepreneurship (3 years)
- Communication (5 years)
- Problem-solving (7 years)
- Strategy (4 years)

Languages

- English Expert
- Nepali Fluent
- Hindi Fluent
- Maithili Expert
- Bhojpuri Fluent

Links

http://instagram.com/mrsauravkt

http://twitter.com/mrsauravkt

https://youtu.be/CPGKfODfUco

Certifications and Licenses

Karate Black Belt

August 2022 to Present

I've earned the rank of 1st DAN (the top rank) in Karate after years of grueling physical, moral and spiritual training.

Groups

Nepal Scouts

April 2020 to Present

As a part of a truly global community, I've spent my time traveling, helping the needy, running health programs, hosting fun camps & promoting nature.